Hello there!
If you're reading this, you're probably wondering what's happened here.
Well, basically, I got so frustrated with our original checkers program that I restarted from scratch.
In the folder "Final Attempt" You will find a PyCheckers.py file which I have worked very hard on for the past couple of hours.
Please do not touch this.
I think it would be best if we each had our own file;

Ben: Sorry to put such a heavy workload on you, but do you think you could program the Play_checkers.py file again?
	It should be significantly easier this time, especially since I now have a Move() class with an isJump() function.
	Don't worry about making a good interface, just make it so that it works well with Gerard's AI and Player methods to make a playable game.

Gerard: Since you have not helped with this project at all yet, I'd like you to program the AI.
	Considering that it just does random stuff, this should be fairly easy.
	You should have two classes, one for the AI agent, and one for the player...
	They should be interchangeable with identically named functions, so that you can call player.move() in the same way as agent.move();
	This is for simplicity, and in hopes that 

Let me know if there's anything I missed in the PyCheckers file, and I'll address it immediately.

Let's try to get this done on time!

-Aaron B.